let questions = []
function SDDQuestions() {
    let sdd_qs = [
        {
            numb: 1,
            question: "What is waterfall method also known as?",
            answer: "Structured development",
            options: [
                "Agile development",
                "End user development",
                "Rapid application development",
                "Structured development",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 2,
            question: "Which method can represent negative numbers in binary?",
            answer: "2's complement",
            options: [
                "IEEE-754",
                "2's complement",
                "Floating point",
                "ASCII",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 3,
            question: "Which of the following is part of the translation of code?",
            answer: "Lexical Analysis",
            options: [
                "Benchmarking",
                "Single-line stepping",
                "Compilation",
                "Lexical Analysis",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 4,
            question: "What is the first stage of software development?",
            answer: "None of the options listed",
            options: [
                "Planning",
                "Implementing",
                "None of the options listed",
                "Maintenance",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 5,
            question: "Which of the following is an intrinsic documentation?",
            answer: "Comments and variable names",
            options: [
                "Dataflow Diagram",
                "Context Diagram",
                "Comments and variable names",
                "IPO Chart",
            ]
        },
    ];
    return sdd_qs
}

function GEOQuestions() {
    let geo_qs = [
        {
            numb: 1,
            question: "Which of the following terms is used to describe where things are and why they are there?",
            answer: "Spatial dimension",
            options: [
                "Spatial dimension",
                "Ecological pattern",
                "Environmental impact",
                "Sustainable development",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 2,
            question: "Which of the following terms includes the concepts of location, spatial organisation, spatial differentiation and distribution?",
            answer: "Spatial patterns",
            options: [
                "Spatial dimension",
                "Spatial exclusion",
                "Spatial patterns",
                "Spatial interdependence",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 3,
            question: "What is the best use of Geographic Information Systems (GIS)",
            answer: "Processing and analysing data spatially",
            options: [
                "Identifying popular trends",
                "Interpreting census data",
                "Analysing and interpreting surveys",
                "Processing and analysing data spatially",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 4,
            question: "Which of the following identifies TWO urban dynamics of change?",
            answer: "Decentralisation and urban renewal",
            options: [
                "Social structure and urban decay",
                "Culture of place and consolidation",
                "Spatial exclusion and sustainability",
                "Decentralisation and urban renewal",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 5,
            question: "Which of the following best describes the term exurbanisation?",
            answer: "Affluent people moving to rural areas",
            options: [
                "The creation of walled estates",
                "A decline in the total population",
                "Affluent people moving to rural areas",
                "A clustering of people with a common culture",
            ]
        },
    ];
    return geo_qs;
}

function IPTQuestions(){
    let ipt_qs =[
        {
            numb: 1,
            question: "The main function of a hub in a network is to connect",
            answer: "computers on the network to share files",
            options: [
                "computers on the network to share files",
                "computers on the network to the internet",
                "computers that are using different protocols",
                "computers that are using different operating systems",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 2,
            question: "Why are parity bits used in data transmission?",
            answer: "To check for errors",
            options: [
                "To check for errors",
                "To convert data into a series of 0s and 1s",
                "To count the number of 0s and 1s in a data packet",
                "To direct data packets from their source to their destination",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 3,
            question: "Which of the following is not a social & ethical issue?",
            answer: "Cyclic redundancy check",
            options: [
                "Changing nature of work",
                "Privacy of the individual",
                "Data quality",
                "Cyclic redundancy check",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 4,
            question: "What does the term 'handshaking' mean?",
            answer: "Establishment of an agreed protocol",
            options: [
                "Modulation of a signal",
                "Process to encrypt a message",
                "Establishment of an agreed protocol",
                "Detection and correction of transmission errors",
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 5,
            question: "Which is the least effective in identifying problems in an existing system?",
            answer: "Writing a troubleshooting guide for users",
            options: [
                "Surveying users",
                "Interviewing participants",
                "Observing participants using the system",
                "Writing a troubleshooting guide for users",
            ]
        },
    ];
    return ipt_qs;

}
